It's so strange to be starting high school today.
I never thought I'd see the day I'd show you this.
Belle from Lipless Plate is now an adult!
She's so cute!
Good afternoon, everyone.
This is Mirina Tanabe from Hensar Soca 46.
I'm sorry for being so sleepy.
Today is the entrance ceremony of my high school.
I hope I can capture the day of the entrance ceremony.
I hope you'll watch until the end!
I have some time in the morning, so I'd like to cook Japanese food.
I'd like to cook some Japanese food.
I'm going to make an omelet and rice.
I'm going to make rice and miso soup.
I want to make miso soup.
I'd like to cook
I'll start with omelet first.
I'll start with the omelet first.
Okay, let's go!
Here we go!
Oh my gosh!
I'm eating a lot of food, so let's go!
I always make it with a little bit of white soup stock and mayonnaise.
I always make it with a little bit of mayonnaise and a little bit of white dashi.
I've never sent you a picture of me cooking.
I've never sent it so far away.
It's very strange.
It's so strange to see myself in front of the camera
cooking in front of the camera.
This feeling
I don't get to show you
I don't get to show you what I'm doing in front of the camera.
I'm very nervous.
At home, I was in charge of making Bean Curd with Bean Sprouts and Fried Eggs.
I used to make those two a lot.
Cut it.
The omelet is ready! The omelet is ready!
It's ready!
Can you see the steam?
It looks so good!
I want to show it to you one more time.
It's really a 360-degree management, so I want you to take a good look at it.
I want you to take a good look at it because it's really 360 degrees.
It's looking good, so I'm going to flip it over, and yes, breakfast is ready.
Grilled salmon and eggs and...
Rice and
Miso soup
and miso soup!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
Delicious.
Starting today...
I'm starting high school today.
It's so strange to start high school today.
It's so strange.
I feel like
I feel like I've become a high school student.
I feel like I'm in a new environment.
A new environment
I'm really nervous.
I get really nervous.
I wonder if there's anyone I can get along with.
That kind of thing.
I'm also anxious.
But with Sumire Miyachi... there's that kind of anxiety, too.
Or Sumire Miyachi.
Tamaki...
It's nice to meet you all.
High school...
That's why you said you're okay.
I think that's what he meant.
I'm sure it's all right.
That's why. So.
I really want this charm.
Today is the entrance ceremony.
I'm not going to wear makeup that clearly because it's a school day.
I'm thinking of doing school makeup.
When I finish high school
I want to go to Disney in uniform.
I think this is from when I was a trainee.
When I was around that age
I was talking with Kaho Fujishima
I was talking with Kaho Fujishima.
I went to Nikko for the school year
I was in high school at Nikko.
just overlap.
That's right.
So...
Kishi and Tsuguji talked about going to Uniform Disney
Kishijiyo and I talked about it.
I'm going...
When I finish high school
I promised her that we'd go to Disney in school uniform
We made a promise.
But the other day...
Kaho remembered.
Let's go to Disneyland in Seifuku next time.
“Let's go to Uniform Disney
And Kaho was...
That made me really happy.
It made me realize that I am now a high school student.
I've been trying to read more recently.
I've been reading a lot.
I like to read books about things.
I like to read books about things, and I've been reading a lot, but maybe I'm reading more now.
I'm probably reading more now.
I like reading books and writing.
It's something I want to work on.
in me.
I'm also a blogger. You have a lot of blogs.
I'll try my best to make you think that my blog is good too.
I'll do my best to make people think it's good. I don't even use that much eyeliner.
You don't even need to draw that much eyeliner.
Let's pack it in!
Pace 5, huh?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Even though it's called school makeup, it's more like my normal makeup.
My makeup
Maybe...
That's why
Once the makeup is done, the next step is the hair.
Next, I would like to set my hair
Next, I'd like to set my hair.
I want to cut the bangs a little bit first.
I want to cut my bangs, so I'm going to cut my bangs a little bit.
I'm going to cut it.
If you put a plastic wrap on your face, the hair won't stick to your face.
I'm going to do it like this.
I'm going to cut it like this.
I never thought I'd see the day I'd show you this.
It's okay.
Put the wrap on.
Cutting it like this.
So that it doesn't fall on the floor
It keeps the hair off the floor and out of your face.
It's really genius.
This is...
Yes, sir.
With this.
The bangs...
Short.
The back.
I'm going to straighten it.
I think the back will be fine too.
Lastly, I'm going to fix the bangs.
The bangs are the best.
The best. The best.
I don't want to move it, and I don't want it to fall apart.
I'll take the longest.
I'll do it.
I'm going to spray it with the intention that I'm not going to let it fall apart.
I'm going to spray it.
I've got it down.
So, I'm going to spray the top one third of the way up here.
I'm going to dry it with a hair dryer.
Now it's pretty hardened.
Next, I'm going to spray the surface.
Now I've got perfect, unmoving bangs.
And that's the end of the haircut.
I've changed into my uniform.
How do you like it?
This time, I chose a uniform that I don't usually get to wear.
A blazer with a white line like this...
It has a bit of a school drama feel to it
I thought it was cute
I chose it.
And then
Like this
Standard
Blue Concealed Skirt
and it's like this
Yes, I'm in uniform.
We're all ready to go!
And now, we are ready to go to school.
I'm off to school!
I'm off!
Now that the entrance ceremony is over
I'm taking a walk outside.
It's over.
The entrance ceremony
Really...
Same age
I don't know anyone my own age.
So... Really.
It was the first time for me to meet you all.
I was so nervous.
Especially today.
Especially...
I've heard about you.
The ceremony was just held, so...
I didn't have to do anything in particular.
The next one ended without any entrance ceremony.
Next time, after the entrance ceremony is over
I would like to go to a certain restaurant to treat myself.
The sun is gradually setting
and night is approaching
Today I'm going to treat myself to a cafe.
I'm going to a café... a café... a very cute café...
It's a very cute cafe!
I've been going to cute cafes for a long time.
I've always enjoyed going to cute cafes.
I still go to such cafes
take pictures and enjoy the food.
It's one of my hobbies
one of my hobbies.
I've always wanted to go to a café
I'm heading to a café I've always wanted to visit
I'm almost there!
Stylish!
Every place is stylish!
Oh!
We are here!
Yes, so this is the place this time. Here we are.
This time, I am going to have my prize sweets here at Cupot Cafe.
Hello.
One person, please.
Pink, pretty.
Amazing.
Yes, thank you. Yes, thank you very much.
Look at this.
The room looks like a shortcake.
It's a really cute space,
Here, too,
check market, and cushions. A really cute space.
There are also cushions
They look good anywhere.
Mmm...
Mnh-mnh.
They're all so cute.
They're dazzling.
I'm sure everyone here is.
Excuse me, orders.
Berry macarons with necklace plates and hot berry gleaming, please.
Yes, you got the message. Here you go.
Thank you very much.
I often come to cafes alone, but I always get nervous when ordering.
It takes me quite a while.
But this time I was able to order very smoothly.
Customer
I'll have a drink.
Thank you very much.
It's the last day dreaming!
Thank you very much for your care at home thank you very much for your care at home thank you very much for your care at home thank you very much for your care at home thank you very much for your care at home thank you very much for your care at home
Please be careful at home
Thank you very much.
This is also a baby macaroon from Sprate
I got it!
They are so cute!
This is the baby macaroon from Sprate that I ordered this time!
So cute!
It's such a waste to eat them!
It's so cute that it's a shame to eat it!
Delicious! Delicious.
This chicken has a strong aroma.
Sweet.
But surprisingly...
With a clean aftertaste.
It's really easy to see.
Shall we eat?
Since we're here...
Not at all.
Bon appétit!
It's so delicious!
There's a lot of cream in it.
It's a lot of time to eat!
It's very satisfying.
You know what I mean?
It's like a scooper.
I think one of these would be enough to satisfy you.
In fact, one tasty piece should be enough to satisfy you.
I met my first classmate today.
We were talking within seconds of meeting.
Some of them were exchanging contact information after the meeting.
Some of them were taking pictures together.
I wondered at what point in time they became such good friends.
I wondered how they could become such good friends.
LOL.
I really want to hear about it.
I went to the entrance ceremony today
I went to the entrance ceremony with my mom.
I talked to her.
It was really difficult at first.
I was like, “No, I can't do it again, I'm alone again,” and when my mother did that to me,
When my mother told me that, she said, “You always do that at the beginning, so it's okay.
So at first, I was worried now that I wouldn't fit in with my classmates.
But I believe in a few months it's going to be all right.
To the 4th graders who worried me so much.
They were worried that I wouldn't be able to go talk to them.
I wanted to go talk to them, but I couldn't.
But I couldn't. I couldn't do it.
Next time
If I have a chance
I'll do my best.
I'll do my best
Anyway
I don't know.
I can't keep up with the latest trends.
Maybe an astronomer? Astronomical profession?
I don't know.
That's why I'm not interested in what's trendy.
I'm not interested in what's trendy.
I'd like to improve on that.
I'm a JK.
I'd like to be in charge of telling Hinatazaka what's trendy before it's too late.
I'll have the last bite.
Thank you for the food and drink, and so on to today's day.
I took a picture of one day on the day of the college ceremony
High school life from now on
I still have a lot of anxieties
I'm going to do my best to have fun
I'll do my best in my work as well.
Thank you for watching until the end!
Please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating!
Please also check out JK Rinashi!
See you soon!